I hurt someone again.
When will I ever truly control myself?
You deserve this.
Don't...
Ah!
Don't move.
I'm
still alive.
You are lucky, Madam.
Senior Medical Maniac said
anyone else
would be pushing up daisies by now.
Ye Qifeng,
stop saying such unlucky things
in the ward.
Qiongqi hurt you.
I will give you an explanation.
Did he do it on purpose?
Qiongqi's true form is a fierce beast.
He relies on Buddhist mantras
to suppress his evil nature.
He just returned to Yanmen,
his aura was unstable,
and he mistook you for an intruder,
so he lost control.
So he couldn't control himself either.
That's no excuse for hurting you.
I know.
But I also know
what it feels like to be dragged around
by something inside your own body.
Uncle,
I don't want to just lie here
waiting for someone to protect me.
The longer I lie here,
the more I feel like
a fragile plate ready to break
at any moment.
If you were a plate, Madam,
you'd be the kind
that jumps up and smashes people.
I'll shut up. The medicine is here.
Focus on recovering first.
Didn't you want to know
about the outside world?
When you're better,
I'll take you there.
Really?
Really.
You're not just going
to carry me out for some sun
and then carry me right back, are you?
Depends on your behavior.
Great.
Sounds like you're going to back out.
Not bad, not bad.
Kong is very perceptive.
This prescription is spot on.
It's because I have a good master.
Hahaha.
Then I will accept you as my disciple.
Yeah.
Our Kong might become
a great doctor in the future.
In the future.
Don't stay cooped up in the room.
Go out for a walk,
you'll recover faster.
Senior Medical Maniac,
am I right?
Go ahead.
Sister,
three more steps
and this candied haw is yours.
Bai, if you talk to me in that tone again,
the first thing I'll do
when I recover is make fish soup.
Here you go, my wise and mighty sister
who is already 80% recovered.
So sweet.
It's good to be alive.
I'm here to apologize.
If you want to punish me,
you can do it anytime.
Wait.
I'm still afraid of you right now.
But I also know
you didn't do it on purpose.
When I'm no longer afraid,
I'll decide how to punish you.
All right.
Everyone in the Yan Sect is protecting me.
But why do I want to go out more and more?
Madam,
the Sect Leader ordered that
you cannot leave the courtyard
until you are fully healed.
I just want to take a look at the streets.
The Sect Leader said last time
you were just asking for directions,
but ended up in the Qiongqi Courtyard.
And the time before that,
you were just taking a walk,
but ended up by the Cold Pool.
Sister,
your 'just'
is usually more than that.
Whose side are you on?
The side of candied haws.
He said he would take me out
when I'm healed.
But I'd be waiting forever
for him to keep his word.
I'm just going out to buy a candied haw,
see the market, and relax.
I won't cause trouble.
Safety first,
running away second,
eating third.
No,
eating should be second.
Running away from home
before fully healing
is indeed quite unprofessional.
But I can't always wait
for others to dictate how I live my life.
Candied haws!
Delicious candied haws!
Give me a stick.
Here you go, Young Master.
By disguising myself as a man,
I finally sneaked out.
It's just as Bai said.
The outside world is so bustling.
What is this place?
It looks so grand.
There must be a lot of
delicious food inside.